# Jr. Web Developer



# Jr. Web Developer

#### EXECUTIVE SUMMARY

I worked as an intern at Digitaktek for 3 months. The company used php, jquery, javascript, html, css as programming languages. I was editing the company's websites for corporate companies. Currently, I have been working in hepapi technology for 1 year. I am making web site arrangements and development with .NET core .

#### PERSONAL INFO

Birth Date: 16.06.1998

Nationality: Turkey

Location: Turkey

#### AREAS OF EXPERTISE

.NET : Expert PHP : Expert HTML : Experienced CSS : Talented

#### KEY SKILLS

**.NET**: 1 have been .NET

PHP: 1 have been PHP

**HTML**: 1 have been HTML

CSS: 1 have been CSS

#### PROFESSIONAL WORK EXPERIENCE

13.03.2022 - 13.03.2022 Digitatek, Turkey

#### Jr. Web Developer

I have supported many corporate web solutions of the company

13.03.2022 - 13.03.2022

Hepapi Technology, United Kingdom

# Jr. Web Developer

I have supported many corporate web solutions of the company

#### EDUCATIONS

13.03.2022 - 13.03.2022

Ankara University, Turkey

# **Computer Programming**

13.03.2022 - 13.03.2022

Anadolu University, Turkey

# **Management Information System**

13.03.2022 - 13.03.2022

Hacettepe Üniversitesi, Bahrain

# **Information Technologies**

#### LANGUAGES

English: A1 (Beginner/Elementary)

**Spanish**: A1 (Beginner/Elementary)

**Turkish**: C2 (Proficient)